http://www.wolfgreenfield.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you.
What information do we collect about you?
We collect basic personal contact and biographical information about you when you register with us or engage with us for legal services. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete client surveys, provide us with feedback, participate in seminars or networking events, or when you use our website. Website usage information is collected using cookies. (For further information about cookies visit allaboutcookies.org.)
When using our website, you may click on links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to our website: wolfgreenfield.com.
When you follow links to other websites you should read their respective privacy policies.
How will we use the information about you?
We collect information about you in order to provide you or your company with legal services, to manage your account and, if you agree, to email you about upcoming events and other services we think may be of interest to you.
We use your information collected from the website to personalize your repeat visits to our website. Wolf Greenfield will not share your information for marketing purposes with other companies.
Marketing
We would like to send you information about products and services which may be of interest to you. Even if you have consented to receive marketing communications, you may opt out at a later date.
You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes.
If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please click here.
Access to your information and correction
You have the right to request a copy of the information we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email or write to us at the address below. We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may also ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.
Changes to our privacy policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on our web site. This privacy policy was last updated on 03 May 2018.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or the information we hold about you:
Wolf Greenfield
c/o Client Services
600 Atlantic Avenue
Boston, MA 02210
617-646-8000
Our website provides general information about Wolf Greenfield and intellectual property law. The content of this site may be considered Attorney Advertising under the laws and rules of professional conduct of the jurisdictions in which we practice. The information on this site does not constitute or contain legal advice and should not be considered legal opinions or a substitute for legal counsel. Prior results do not guarantee a similar outcome.
